var questions = [{
    "question" : "Which one can not consider as a Noun ?",
    "option1" : "A thing",
    "option2" : "A place",
    "option3" : "An animal",
    "option4" : "An action",
    "answer" : "4"
}, {
    "question" : "Verbs are using to ?",
    "option1" : "Replace a Noun",
    "option2" : "Describe a Noun",
    "option3" : "Show action",
    "option4" : "Connect words",
    "answer" : "3"
}, {
    "question" : "Which one it the not a Adjective ?",
    "option1" : "Angry",
    "option2" : "Quickly",
    "option3" : "Helthy",
    "option4" : "Good",
    "answer" : "2"
}, {
    "question" : "Choose the Adverb ?",
    "option1" : "Nearly",
    "option2" : "Healthy",
    "option3" : "Interesting",
    "option4" : "John",
    "answer" : "1"
}, {
    "question" : "Which one is Used with a Article ?",
    "option1" : "Brown cat",
    "option2" : "The cat",
    "option3" : "Cat runs",
    "option4" : "Little cat",
    "answer" : "2"
}, {
    "question" : "Which on is not a Preposition ?",
    "option1" : "since",
    "option2" : "between",
    "option3" : "an",
    "option4" : "after",
    "answer" : "3"
}, {
    "question" : "Conjunctions are use to ?",
    "option1" : "Connect words",
    "option2" : "Connect phases",
    "option3" : "Connect sentences",
    "option4" : "All of them",
    "answer" : "4"
}, {
    "question" : "Choose the interjection ?",
    "option1" : "I",
    "option2" : "Oops",
    "option3" : "an",
    "option4" : "angry",
    "answer" : "2"
}, {
    "question" : "Which one is the Pronoun ?",
    "option1" : "I",
    "option2" : "Quickly",
    "option3" : "John",
    "option4" : "Run",
    "answer" : "1"
}, {
    "question" : "Choose the interjection ?",
    "option1" : "above",
    "option2" : "since",
    "option3" : "of",
    "option4" : "None of them",
    "answer" : "4"
}

]